[
    {
        "question": "lata",
        "answer": "tin",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "deletrear",
        "answer": "spell",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "incluso",
        "answer": "including",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Aun",
        "answer": "Even",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronda",
        "answer": "Round (of golf) or boxing Ring",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Largo",
        "answer": "Long",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Medir",
        "answer": "Measure",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "buque",
        "answer": "Boquet, Ship",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "lot/batch",
        "answer": "lote",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Democrat",
        "answer": "democrata",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "break",
        "answer": "la raptura",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "the vote",
        "answer": "el voto",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "the official (person)",
        "answer": "el funcionario",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "the correspondent",
        "answer": "el corresponsal",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "ground",
        "answer": "el terreno",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "really",
        "answer": "realmente",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Furthermore",
        "answer": "Ademas",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sense (of a word), Sense (of taste/sight etc)",
        "answer": "sentido",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The matter, issue, subject",
        "answer": "Asunto",
        "box_location": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Demons",
        "answer": "Demonios",
        "box_location": 1
    }
]